wetandpissy.com 2013-06-29

# Privacy policy | Wetandpissy.com

Members Access Models: **562**    |    Scenes: **713**    |    Videos: **700**    |    Hours: **209h 9' 57''**    |    Pics: **47897** All Our Girls Love To Show Their Hot Piss!

To protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to Weliketosuck.com. On some pages, you can purchase a Membership to Weliketosuck.com, make requests, and register to receive access and materials. The type of personal information collected at these pages are name, age, email address, gender, etc.

We use Epoch.com, who will obtain additional information such as your address and credit card data. The information collected by Weliketosuck.com is used solely for the creation and maintenance of your Membership account. We do not sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose your personal data. That information collected by Epoch.com is used for the purpose of processing payment of your Membership to Weliketosuck.com. You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain it by logging on to the right user account pages, where the informations was collected. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information simply by modifying that information online.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You assures to have all rights for the submission of data and their publication to the system of Weliketosuck.com. You agree to save harmless Weliketosuck.com from all costs, which result from offences against it.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send an email: [support@weliktosuck.com](mailto:support@weliktosuck.com).
